Guide to the Duke Management Company records, 1980-1993
Duke University. University Archives
- Container List
  - Stratmor Group/Strategic Mortgage Finance Group Inc. (Box 10)
  - Sunshine, Gene: Johns Hopkins University (Box 10)
  - Sunwestern Investment Group (Box 10)
  - John Supple, 1991 July 25 (Box 10)
  - Sussman, Arthur M. (EJM) (Box 10)
  - Synertech Group, Inc. (Box 10)
  - TDH III Limited (from Joel Fleishman) (Box 10)
  - Teamer SR, Charles C. (VP Fiscal Affairs, Dillard Univ.) (Box 10)
  - Stuart Torgovnick (Box 10)
  - Alexandra Treadaway (Box 10)
  - Treasurer's Office Reorganization, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Executive Vice President: Organization (Box 10)
  - Treasurer's Office Reorganization, 1984- (Box 10)
  - Treasurer's Office Studies--Offitt (Box 10)
  - Treasurer's Office Studies--Cambridge (Box 10)
  - Cambridge Associates Study: T. Clough (Box 10)
  - Trott, John (EJM) (Box 10)
  - United Asset Management Corporation (Box 10)
  - University Science Partners: Venture Capital (Box 10)
  - Venture Capital (Box 10)
  - Venture Capital - In-house/Investment Committee Meeting, 1989 March 3 (Box 10)
  - Venture Capital: Tom Rhodes (Box 10)
  - Venture Capital: Duke (Box 10)
  - Baxter Meeting, 1989 August 16 (Box 10)
  - Venture Economics (Box 10)
  - Steve Ritterbush, Venture Fund, Washington, 1992 June 25 (Box 10)
  - Professor Voronov, 1991 December 6 (Box 10)
  - Investment Vortech (Box 10)
  - Wall, Edwin "Craig" (Box 10)
  - Investments: Welch Allyn, Inc. (Richard W. Newman) (Box 10)
  - Investments: K.L. Whitney Co. (Box 10)
  - Willis Jr., William H. (Box 10)
  - WM (World Markets) Company (Box 10)
  - Investments: WSW Fund (Box 10)
  - Duke Management Company: Review Committee Report, 1999 February (Box 10)
  - Computing: General Correspondence (Box 11)
  - Computing: Reorganization of Computing, 1985 (Box 11)
  - EJM Software (Box 11)
  - Computer Telephone Switch Committee (Box 11)
  - Allen Building Office Network (Box 11)
  - Computing at Duke Committee: Interim Report, 1989 December (Box 11)
  - Computers: Virus (Box 11)
  - Computers: Computer Sales to Students (Box 11)
  - Computing: Stead Letter (Governance of Information Systems), 1989 January 17 (Box 11)
  - CDC Consultants Meet with CEO, 1989 November 30 (Box 11)
  - Computing: Project Nexus (Box 11)
  - Computing: Reorganization of Computing, 1989 ("Prior to creation of CDC") (Box 11)
  - Computing at Duke Committee: General Correspondence (Box 11)
  - Contemporary Computer Project (Box 11)
  - CDC: Outside Consultant Report (Box 11)
  - Computers: Provost's Task Force on Networking (Box 11)
  - R. Townsend Davis, Jr. (Box 11)
  - DUFS: Marriott (Box 11)
  - DUFS Catering Office (Box 11)
  - Duke University Food Services (Box 11)
  - East Campus: Food Court (Box 11)
  - East Campus: Electric Power (Box 11)
  - Economic Impact of Duke in the Durham Community (Box 11)
  - Engineering School (Box 11)
  - Executive Committee of the Academic Council (Box 11)
  - Faculty Governance Committee, 1988 March 2 (Box 11)
  - Financial Planning for University Employees (Box 11)
  - Formula: Arts and Sciences (Box 11)
  - Formulas: General (Box 11)
  - Formula: Parent Incentive Agreement (Box 11)
  - Formulas (Box 11)
  - Formula Discs, Phillip Griffiths, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Formula: Law School (Box 11)
  - Formula Revision: Campbell Committee, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Fringe Benefits: Staff Fringe Benefits Committee (Box 11)
  - Fringe Benefit: Athletic Department Subsidy (Box 11)
  - Fringe Benefit Costs (Box 11)
  - Fringe Benefit Pool (Box 11)
  - Fringe Benefit Rate (Box 11)
  - Renegotiate Fringe Rates: BC/BS Portion (Box 11)
  - Governance Committee (Box 11)
  - Fuqua Hotel Working File (Box 11)
  - Duke Artists Series: Advisory Board (Box 12)
  - Duke Chapel: Aeolian Organ (Box 12)
  - Duke Press (Box 12)
  - SACS Accreditation Meeting, 1988 October 18 (Box 12)
  - Metrosport: Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Racquet Club Zoning (Box 12)
  - Moore, Julius/Moore, Charles (Friends of Mary Semans) (Box 12)
  - Larry Nelson (Box 12)
  - Overhead Cost Recovery: Correspondence, 1988- (Box 12)
  - Indirect Cost Audit (Box 12)
  - Operating Boards (Box 12)
  - WGA, Donelan, RS, EJM Olympic Trials, 1990 May 22 (Box 12)
  - Olympics: Track and Field (Box 12)
  - Physics Department: Madey & Formula (Box 12)
  - Dean's Involvement in Budget Process (Box 12)
  - Planning: Academic Plan (Box 12)
  - University-Industry Guidelines, Proposed Policy, 1985 October (Box 12)
  - Renovation: Project Costs (Box 12)
  - Sullivan Trust (Box 12)
  - Taxation: Scholarships, Fellowships, Stipends (Box 12)
  - Garrison Telephone Switch (Box 12)
  - 5ES Telephone Switch (Box 12)
  - LAN Report Problems (Box 12)
  - Bluenet (Box 12)
  - Telcom: Satellite Dish Receiver (Box 12)
  - Electronic Phone System 3100L (Box 12)
  - Telcom: AT&T Contract (Box 12)
  - Tele-com: Advisory Committee (Box 12)
  - Telcom Renovations (Box 12)
  - Travel: Frequent Flier Points (Box 12)
  - Telcom: General Correspondence (Box 12)
  - Travel Agency Meet, 1989 February 27 (Box 12)
  - Anspach Travel Bureau (Box 12)
  - Travel Agency: Roy Rodwell/Argo (Box 12)
  - Travel Agency (Box 12)
  - Trading Tuition for Work (Box 12)
  - Tuition Benefit: Special Cases (Box 12)
  - Duke Forest: ULI Report (Box 12)
  - Objections to ULI Report (Box 12)
  - ULI Post Dinner Get-Together/President's House, 1987 February 27 (Box 12)
  - ULI: Carley, David/Edwin Jones/Clay, Jim (Box 12)
  - ULI: General Background (Box 12)
  - ULI: Panelists' Correspondence (Box 12)
  - ULI: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 12)
  - Haw River (Duke Forest): Walk-through&DE, CBH, EJM (Box 12)
  - ULI 1985-86: Correspondence (Box 12)
  - Union Management Local 77 (Box 12)
  - Wallace, Andy (Box 12)
  - Williams, George (Box 12)
  - Asbestos Damage (Box 13)
  - Ad Hoc Steering Committee: Ballpark (Box 13)
  - Bonds 1987: Rating Agency Visits (Box 13)
  - Correspondence Bonds (Box 13)
  - Oden Conference Call: Bonds, 1988 February (Box 13)
  - S&P Moody's Meeting (Box 13)
  - Dr. Sam Cook Phone Call on Bonds (Box 13)
  - Rating Agency Visit and Dinner (Box 13)
  - Bonds 1987 Series: First Boston (Box 13)
  - Rating Dinner, 1987 September 29 (Box 13)
  - Bond Rating Visit, 1987 September 30-31 (Box 13)
  - 1987 Bonds: Internal Plans for Proceeds (Box 13)
  - 1986 Tax Exempt Bond Act: Papers Relative To (Box 13)
  - Standard & Poor's NY, 1987 October 19 (Box 13)
  - Bond Closing, New York, 1987 November 24 (Box 13)
  - Bond Meeting, 1987 August 20 (Box 13)
  - Bonds: Bond Contenders (Box 13)
  - Tony Duke, Jr.: Fiduciary Trust (Box 13)
  - Bond Meeting, 1987 August 5 (Box 13)
  - Bonds: Legal Opinions (Box 13)
  - Bonds: Bankers Trust, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Investments: Bronx National Bank (Box 13)
  - Old Chemistry Renovations (Box 13)
  - Child Care Center (Box 13)
  - Frank Church (Box 13)
  - Computing: Academic (Box 13)
  - Information Services Committee: Executive Committee Of (Box 13)
  - Computing at Duke Committee (CDC): Initial Charge adn Committee Make-Up (Box 13)
  - Debt Financing and Computer Equipment (Box 13)
  - Computer Surcharge (Box 13)
  - Computers: PDC Purchase (Box 13)
  - Integration of Computing and TelCom (Box 13)
  - Year-End Appropriations (Box 13)
  - Pathology Department: Internal Audit (Box 13)
  - Pathology: General Correspondence (Box 13)
  - Macronex (Dolph Adams and Sal Pizzo): Venture Cap Firm (Box 13)
  - Listening Post (Box 13)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield: New Premium Rates (Box 14)
  - Public Safety Board (Box 14)
  - Alcoholic Beverages Policy (Box 14)
  - Policy: Campus Usage (Box 14)
  - Policy: Contractor Performance and Reinstatement (Box 14)
  - Policy: Corporate Records (Box 14)
  - Policy: Maternity Leave (Box 14)
  - Safe Driving Policy (Box 14)
  - Policy: Scientific Fraud (Box 14)
  - Policy: Short Term Disability (Box 14)
  - Policy: Work Rules (Box 14)
  - Financial Problems (Box 14)
  - JA: PAG (Box 14)
  - Accounting in Academic Sector (Box 14)
  - Provost Office: Financial Matters, Plans, etc., 1988 (Box 14)
  - Provost Office: Financial Matters, Plans, etc., 1987 (Box 14)
  - Mark D. Cowan (Box 14)
  - 1989/90 Year-End Appropriations (Box 14)
  - FY 1988/89 Year-End Appropriations and Special Requests (Box 14)
  - 1988 Year-End Appropriations (Box 14)
  - DU Working Hours (Box 14)
  - CUPA Achievement Award (Box 14)
  - 1987/88 Budget Forecast: Total Compensation (Box 14)
  - Total Compensation Proposal (Box 14)
  - Total Compensation (Box 14)
  - Charitable Giving (Box 14)
  - Center for Living: Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 14)
  - Finch Yeager Building (Box 14)
  - Center for Living: Meeting with Drs. Anlyan, Griffiths, Wallace, Greenfield, and Putman (Box 14)
  - DUPAC (Box 14)
  - The DUPAC Story (Box 14)
  - Institute for Living (Box 14)
  - Center for Living Acreage Question (Box 14)
  - Stedman Gift: Center for Living (Box 14)
  - Center for Living: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Center for Living: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 14)
  - Human Resources: Toby Kahr (Box 14)
  - Crowe Hotel Development Company Porfolio (Box 15)
  - Duke Chronicle, 1981 October (Box 15)
  - WRT Working Paper (Duke Forest), 1988 August (Box 15)
  - Duke University Campus Planning Studies (Draft) (Box 16)
  - Proposed Campus Plan and Implementation Strategy: East Campus, 1987 (Box 16)